Guide to the Theta Chi Records, 1968-2002 and undated UA.31.22.0016
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Theta Chi records
1968-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Theta Chi. Gamma Sigma Chapter (Duke University)
UA.31.22.0016
4 Linear Feet
The Theta Chi Records are a collection of photographs and papers created by the Duke University chapter of the fraternal organization Theta Chi.
Historical note
The Gamma Sigma chapter of the Theta Chi fraternal organization was founded at Duke in 1949. The chapter disaffiliated with the national organization and moved off Duke's campus in 2006.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Theta Chi Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in May, 2014.
Collection Overview
The collection includes pledge paddlebooks, notebooks, rush materials, and composite photographs of members of the fraternity.
Initiations (into trades, societies, etc.); Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc; Greek letter societies -- North Carolina -- Durham; Theta Chi. Gamma Sigma Chapter (Duke University)
- Papers, 1976-2001 and undated; 1
  - Journal, circa 2000 (Box 1)
  - Journal, circa 2001 (Box 1)
  - Paddle Book, undated (Box 1)
  - Notebook, circa 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Paddle Book, circa 2001 (Box 1)
  - IFC, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Rush Workshop, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Ledger, 1976 and undated (Box 2)
- Photographs, 1968-2002; 2
  - Composite Photographs, 1968-1977 (Oversize-folder 1, Box 2)
  - Composite Photographs, 1976-1999 (Box 2)
  - Composite Photograph, 1983 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Composite Photograph, 1984 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Composite Photograph, 1985 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Composite Photograph, 1986 (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Composite Photograph, 1987 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Composite Photograph, 1988 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Composite Photograph, 1989-1990 (Oversize-folder 7)
  - Composite Photograph, 1990-1991 (Oversize-folder 8)
  - Composite Photograph, 1992-1993 (Oversize-folder 9)
  - Composite Photograph, 1993-1994 (Oversize-folder 10)
  - Composite Photograph, 1994-1995 (Oversize-folder 11)
  - Composite Photograph, 1995-1996 (Oversize-folder 12)
  - Composite Photograph, 1996-1997 (Oversize-folder 13)
  - Composite Photograph, 1997-1998 (Oversize-folder 14)
  - Composite Photograph, 1998-1999 (Oversize-folder 15)
  - Composite Photograph, 1999-2000 (Oversize-folder 16)
  - Composite Photograph, 2000-2001 (Oversize-folder 17)
  - Composite Photograph, 2001-2002 (Oversize-folder 18)